Correctional Association of New York; Records apap014
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Project Files, 1974-1988; 6; 3.33 cubic ft.
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Mental Health - Westchester County, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Mentally Impaired Prisoners, 1979-1987 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Mentally Impaired Prisoners - Commission on Quality of Care for the Mentally Disabled, 1985-1987 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Mentally Impaired Prisoners - Connelly/Feldman Report, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Mentally Impaired Prisoners - Feldman Report, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Mentally Impaired Prisoners - H.E.L.P. and Other Family Groups, 1985-1987 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Mentally Impaired Prisoners - Legislative Hearings, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Mentally Impaired Prisoners - Meeting, ca. 1985 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Mentally Impaired Prisoners - Mentally Impaired in New York's Prisons, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Mentally Impaired Prisoners - Mentally Impaired in New York's Prisons - Reactions to Report, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Mentally Impaired Prisoners - Other State Programs, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Mentally Impaired Prisoners - Prisoners' Legal Services, etc., 1985-1987 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Mentally Impaired Prisoners - Problems and Treatment, 1980-1985 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Mentally Impaired Prisoners - Report Mailing List, etc., 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Mentally Impaired Prisoners - Retarded Offenders, 1973-1982 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Mentally Impaired Prisoners - Steelman, Diane - Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Mentally Impaired Prisoners - Texas - Ruiz v. Estelle, 1984-1986 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Miscellaneous, 1985-1987 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - New York City Jails, 1983-1986 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - New York State Mental Health System, 1984-1987 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - New York State Office of Mental Health Forensic Services, 1983-1986 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - New York State Office of Mental Health Forensic Services, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - New York State Office of Mental Health - Level of Care Study, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - New York State Prisons - General, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Notes, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Other Research Projects, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Outline, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Parole, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Proposal Summary, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Retreat, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Retreat/Colloquium, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Survey - Attica [RESTRICTED], 1985-1987 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Survey - Auburn, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Survey - Bedford Hills, 1981-1987 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Survey - Central New York Psychiatric Center, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Survey - Clinton, 1983-1985 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Survey - Downstate, 1982-1986 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Survey - Elmira, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Survey - Fishkill, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Survey - Great Meadow/Comstock, 1982-1986 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Survey - Green Haven, 1978-1985 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Survey - Sing Sing (Ossining), 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Survey - Sullivan, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Survey - Wende [RESTRICTED], 1985-1987 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - TASC (Treatment Alternatives to Street Crime, Westchester County), 1988 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - TASC, 1988? (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - TASC - Interview Questions, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - TASC - Interview with H. Goldstein, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - TASC - Interviews, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - TASC - Probation Agreement, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - TASC - Program Narrative, 1988? (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - TASC - Staff Meeting, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - TASC - Statistics, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Prison Mental Hygiene Project - Unsuccessful Funding Proposals, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Prison Overcrowding Project, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Prison Overcrowding Project, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Prison Overcrowding Project - News Clippings, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Prison Overcrowding Project - Personnel Search, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Prison Overcrowding Project - Press Releases and Testimony, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Prison Overcrowding Project - Proposals, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Prison Overcrowding Project - Questions and Answers, 1982-1984 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Prison Overcrowding Project - Vermeulen, Jean - Correspondence, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Prison Overcrowding Project - Vermeulen, Jean - Correspondence (1 of 2) [RESTRICTED], 1983-1984; 2 folders (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Prison Overcrowding Project - Vermeulen, Jean - Correspondence (2 of 2) [RESTRICTED], 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Prison Overcrowding Project - Vermeulen, Jean - Correspondence, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Prison Overcrowding Project - Vermeulen, Jean - Reports, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Prison Overcrowding Project - Vermeulen, Jean - Testimony on Determinate Sentencing, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Prison Overcrowding/Public Policy Project, 1975-1987 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Project Summaries, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Project Summaries and Analyses, 1980-1982 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Proposed Project - Prisoner's Rights Litigation, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Proposed Project - Visits to Institutions and Field Services, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Proposed Projects, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Proposed Projects - Concept Papers, ca. 1985 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - State Planning Project, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - State Planning Project - Clark Foundation, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - State Planning Project - Pochoda, Dan - Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - State Planning Project - Prison Population Explosion - Advance Copies Mailed, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - State Planning Project - Prison Population Explosion - Correspondence, 1982-1984 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - State Planning Project - Prison Population Explosion in New York State, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - State Planning Project - Prison Population Explosion - Report Mailing, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - State Planning Project - Prison Population Explosion, 1982; typescript (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - State Planning Project - Resource Materials, 1975-1981 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - State Planning Project - Resumes, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - State Planning Project - Rikers Island, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - State Planning Project - Vouchers, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Subject Files, 1947-1988; 1970-1985; 7; 11 cubic ft.
  This series consists of a wide array of material concerning correctional facility operations, criminal law and the criminal courts, juvenile offenders, rehabilitation programs, and other subjects in which the Correctional Association was interested. Documents include published reports, news clippings, newsletters of other organizations, affidavits, and brochures. Correspondence from various Correctional Association personnel is scattered throughout this series. Most of it is routine (e.g., requests for copies of reports), but some of the files dating from the 1960s contain copies of letters detailing specific aspects of New York State criminal law and correctional facility policies.
  - Ad Hoc Committee on Gun Control, 1967-1970 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Advisory Committee on Criminal Sanctions, Report, Part I, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - After Ossining: A Legislative Response with Recommendations, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - AIDS in Correctional Facilities: Issues and Options, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Alabama - Psychological Assessment Services, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Alcohol and Alcoholism: A Police Handbook, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Alcoholism and the Administration of Justice, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Alcoholism and Correction, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Alcohol Ingestion, Alcoholism and Traffic Accidents, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Alliance for a Safer New York, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Alliance for a Safer New York - Jobs Committee, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Alliance for a Safer New York - Jobs Committee, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Alternative Sentencing, 1979-1981 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Alternative Sentencing, 1982-1984 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Alternative Sentencing - New York Center on Sentencing Alternatives, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Alternatives to Prison Report - Outline, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - American Bar Association, 1973-1984; 2 folders (Box 1, Folder 17-18)
  - American Correctional Association Winter Conference, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - American Prisons and Jails - ABT Report, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Analysis of Actual Expenditures for New York State Prisons, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Andrew Glover Youth Program, 1983-1988 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Atlantic Mutual Insurance Company, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Attica 1982: An Analysis of Current Conditions in New York State Prisons (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Attica 1982 Report - C.A.'s Response to Commissioner's Criticism (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Attica 1982 Report - Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Attica: A Report on Conditions, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Attica Correctional Facility [RESTRICTED], 1982-1986 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Background Paper on Narcotics Addiction, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Bail, 1970-1973 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Bail, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Bail and Summons, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Bail Bond, 1958-1974; 2 folders (Box 1, Folder 33-34)
  - Bail Project - Legal Aid, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Behavioral Emergencies, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Bibliographies, 1973-1983 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Bloom and Gelb, Inc., 1977 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Board of Social Ministry, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Bringing Criminal Administration out of the Dark, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Bronx Correctional Facility - Proposed, 1983-1985 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Budget Education Project - Toward a Crime Prevention Strategy, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Budget Education Project - Toward a Crime Prevention Strategy - Correspondence, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Budget Education Project - Toward a Crime Prevention Strategy - Media, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Burger, Warren - Chief Justice, U.S. Supreme Court, 1980-1983 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - California, 1983-1987 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Campaign for Common Sense in Criminal Justice, 1984-1986 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Campaign for Common Sense in Criminal Justice, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Campaign for Common Sense in Criminal Justice - Criticism of New York State Sentencing Guidelines, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Campaign for Common Sense in Criminal Justice - New York State Drug Laws, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - CANY - Annual Report to the Legislature, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - CA Report - Attica and Commissioner's Response, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - CA Statement - Price of Punishment, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - CA Statement - Prison Population Explosion in NYS, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Capital Punishment, 1984-1987 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Capital Punishment - Executions - Statistics, 1949-1962 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Career Criminals, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Cell Block Theatre Corporation, 1971-1973 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Center for Governmental Research, Inc. - Study of Future of Pretrial Release Services in New York State, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Center for Studies in Criminal Justice, Chicago, Illinois, 1965-1969 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Challenge of Fair and Effective Criminal Administration, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Changes We Should Make in Our Correctional System, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Changes in Policies in the United States in Dealing with Public Intoxication, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Chemical Bank, 1983-1985 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Chicago State University - Proposed Corrections Program, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Chronic Police Court Alcoholic, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - The Church and the Homosexual, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Church of Gethsemane - Dunamis, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Circle Project, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Citizen Involvement in the Administration of Justice, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Citizens' Budget Commission, 1982-1984 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Citizens' Committee for Children of New York, 1962-1972 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Citizens' Committee on Prison Overcrowding, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Citizens' Committee on Prison Overcrowding, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Citizens' Committee on Prison Overcrowding, 1983-1986 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Citizens' Committee on Prison Overcrowding - Press Conference/Release, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Citizens' Committee on Prison Overcrowding - Membership Mailings and Mailing Lists, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Citizens' Crime Commission, 1980-1984 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Citizens' Crime Commission and CANY - Sentencing Proposals, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Civic Assembly, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Civil Liberties, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Committee for Economic Development, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Committee for Modern Courts, 1972-1973; 2 folders (Box 2, Folder 46-47)
  - Committee for Public Counsel Services (Massachusetts), First Annual Report, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Community Corrections Act, 1978-1983 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Community Corrections Act, 1978-1984 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Community Council of Greater New York, Program Plan 1985 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Community Service, 1980-1985 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Community Service Society of New York, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Community Service Society of New York, Alternatives to Incarceration, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Community Service Society of New York, The Changing Face of Poverty, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Comprehensive Correctional Planning Model, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Comprehensive Pay Scales - New York State, New York City, and Federal, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Conditions of Confinement, 1983-1987 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Conferences, 1971-1975 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Conferences Attended, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Connecticut, 1965-1967 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Connecticut State Prison Association, News and Views, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Contracting for the Operation of Private Prisons: Pros and Cons, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Contributions - Tally Sheets, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Commitment "In lieu of" Fine or Bond, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Comradeship Courts and Related Innovations in the Soviet Union?, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Conference: Staff Participation, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Correction and the Alcoholic, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Correctional Programs, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Correctional Service Federation, 1970-1980 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Corresponding Secretary's Report for 1972 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Cost of Crime: Jails (Television Script), 1976 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Cost of Justice (Bronx County), ca. 1980 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Cost of Punishment, 1977-1980 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Council on Legal Education for Professional Responsibility, Inc., 1970 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - County Programming for Alternatives to Incarceration, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Courts and Pubic Drunkenness - The Outlook, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Court Employment Project, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Court Orders, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Courts, 1968-1973 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Courts, Task Force on, Report, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Crime and Punishment: The Public's View, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Crime Statistics, 1978-1985 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Crime Statistics, 1979-1997 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Crimes with No Victims, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Criminal Justice Agency, 1981-1984 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Criminal Justice Bibliography, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Criminal Justice Institute, Inc, ca. 1985 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Criminal Justice Organization Newsletters and Correspondence, 1984-1987 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Criminal Justice Reference Library, Newsletter, 1971-1983 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Criminal Justice System, 1985-1987 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Criminal Justice System - Problem of Balance, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Criminal Responsibility and the Alcoholic, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Cult of Chemical Comorts?, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Currie, Elliot - Articles, 1982-1985 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - A Day in Court Means a Day in the Pens, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Decline of the Rehabilitative Ideal: Penal Policy and Social Purpose, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Delaware Council on Crime and Justice, Inc., Bulletin, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Detention of Individuals Pending Trial, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Dimensions of Drug Dependence in the United Kingdom, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Directory of New York State Criminal Justice Agencies - Request, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Ditchley Foundation (England), 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Djini, Andja, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Double-celling (Overcrowding), 1982 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Downstate Correctional Facility, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Drugs, Drug Testing, Drug Laws, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Drug Scene UK 1969 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Drunkenness Offense, The Legal Position in the USA, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Early Release, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Electronically Monitored In - house Confinement, ca. 1980 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Evaluation, ca. 1975 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Evaluation of Project Anti-Recidivism, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Fact Sheet on Capital Punishment, Undated (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - False Arrest, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - False Sense of Security: A Press Briefing on Crime and Prisons, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Feasibility of a Correctional Ombudsman, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Federal Crime Legislation, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Federal Prisons Offer Training in Office Work, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Federation of Protestant Welfare Agencies, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Fellowship Center, ca. 1980 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Figgie Report on Fear of Crime: America Afraid, Part I, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Findings of Ad Hoc Committee on Youth Needs, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Fines in Sentencing, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Floating Foundation of Photography - Three Prisons Exhibit, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Focus on Health Agencies, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Fortune Society News, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Foundation Reports (Material), 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - General Secretary's Report for 1965 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - General Secretary's Report for 1966 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - General Secretary's Report for 1967 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - General Secretary's Report for 1970, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - General Secretary's Report for 1971 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - "Georgia Residents' Attitudes Toward the Death Penalty, the Disposition of Juvenile Offenders and Related Issues", 1986 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Gideon Decision (Study of Recidivism and Socio - cultural Change), 1965 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Governmental Attitude and Action toward Prostitution, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Governor's Special Committee on Criminal Offenders, Observations on Preliminary Report of, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Governor's Task Force on Alcoholism Treatment in Criminal Justice - Report, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Green, William - Resume, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Greyhound, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - GRI - Governmental Research Institute, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - GROW - Group Relations Ongoing Workshops, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Guidelines on the Use of Arrest and Conviction Records as Job Selection Criteria, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Gun Control, 1980-1985 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Half-Way Houses, 1963-1972 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Harris, M. Kay - Articles, 1979-1981 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Heroin Use in a Provincial Town - One Year Later, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Herstedvester Detention Center (Netherlands), 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Hoffa, James - Testimony, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Home Detention, 1984-1986 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Homicide, 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Homicide in New York State, 1981; 1983 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Homosexuality, 1969-1973 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Human Resources Administration Services, Commissioner's Statement on, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Human Services Management Institute, Inc., ca. 1980 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - ICC Link, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Illegal Aliens - Incarceration, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Incarceration - Cost Effectiveness, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Incarceration Costs, 1982-1984 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Inmate Population Distribution, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Inmate Problems, News Clippings, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Inquiry into the Juvenile Centers Operated by the Office of Probation, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Interfaith Coalition for Equal Justice, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - "Inside America's Toughest Prison", 1986 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - International Council on Alcohol and Addictions, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Is the Alcoholic Immune from Criminal Prosecution, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Jails, 1965-1969 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Jail Reform - National Coalition, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Jailing the Drunken Alcoholic - It's "Cruel and Unusual Punishment", 1966 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Jails/Jail Inmates, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Jails - Population Statistics, 1984-1986 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Jaycees, 1971-1975 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Job Problems of Ex-offenders, 1969-1976; 2 folders (Box 4, Folder 45-46)
  - Job Training, 1967-1973 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Judges on Prisons, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Judicial Conference, 1967-1971 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Judicial Selection, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Justifiable Abortions, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Juvenile Courts, 1962-1967 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Juvenile Delinquency, 1964-1972 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Juvenile Detention Association, National, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Juvenile Detention Centers, 1968-1972 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Juvenile Detention Panel, 1970-1971; 2 folders (Box 5, Folder 1-2)
  - Juveniles, 1970-1972 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Juveniles, 1973-1984 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Juveniles, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Juveniles and Juvenile Justice System, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Lasker Decision - House of Detention for Men, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 7)